so I put it out there that I wanted to
roast a big city police department and
the only one to step up and say Yes was
the home of America's very first police
force Boston a city that I've loved
since going to college there but on the
morning I arrived an officer was shot
and tensions were running High I am at
33 shot you know this individual just
shot one of our officers and the
officers were able to tackle him and not
use deadly force I don't know the
details of what happened in Dorchester
but cop get shot they could have they
could have killed the guy his partner
could have killed the guy you know the
officers rean him down and tackled him
when they could have used deadly force I
I I like to say uh you know we're a
compassionate department and we care
about human life and I think the public
realizes that Boston used to have a bad
reputation well when I came on the job
we had 160 homicides we had 38 this year
Chicago had 500 Baltimore had
344 so the stricter gun laws and the
community work we're doing is really
making a difference why would you let me
come in and roast the Boston Police
Department well I I would because you
know I Want to Break The Stereotype out
there that uh you know we're the bad
guys I wanted people to see that what's
playing out Across the Nation isn't what
the Boston police are we don't mind you
making fun of us because I want the
public to know we're real people
you got a nose for Crime I know and ears
for it
too now that the brass was on board I
was revved up and ready to address the
rank and file during an afternoon roll
call and give them a few laughs before
they hit the
streets how are you
everybody I'll make this quick as I know
most of you are double
parked thank you for letting me come
here this is really cool I've never
performed in front of an entire room
full of YouTube celebrities
before this would be so much better if
you guys just came into the middle of
the room all right fine you guys also
have a rich criminal history in this
town you had the Boston Tea Party here
Whitey buer was from here Tom Brady's
from
here oh come on that one really let the
air out of the room
huh and let's be real if Whitey bulger's
name had been Blackie buer they would
have caught him a lot quicker
Jesus Christ there's obviously a problem
between the cops and the community
across the country right now and that's
what I'm here because that really
bothers me and it really bothers me when
some people say that all cops are racist
of course that's not true most of you
are just sticks to
everybody all
right all right well thanks for coming
all right thanks you guys holy that
sucked hasn't there been enough bombing
in Boston well it turns out that right
before I got to Town the policeman's
Union found a picture of me at that
black lives matter rally and profiled me
as a cop haer they even posted a
bulletin in all the precincts and sent
an email to every cop in town telling
them to stay away from me with no
cameras allowed I spent hours
negotiating my comedy special at of a
hostage
[Applause]
situation